<?xml version="1.0"?>
<quiz>

	<!-- Test of questions -->

	<!-- 1 -->
	<examSet>
		<question>What is a computer algorithm?</question>
		<options>A) step-by-step procedure for calculations
B) a collection of data items stored in memory
C) some crap
D) more crap
		</options>
		<answer>A) is correct</answer>
	</examSet>
	
	<!-- 2 -->
	<examSet>
		<question>What is a data structure?</question>
		<options>A) some crap
B) more crap 
C) step-by-step procedure for calculations
D) a collection of data items stored in memory
		</options>
		<answer>D) is correct</answer>
	</examSet>
	
	<!-- 3 -->
	<examSet>
		<question>Make something up!?</question>
		<options>A) some crap
B) more crap 
C) :D
D) :)
		</options>
		<answer>all options incorrect :/</answer>
	</examSet>
	
	<!-- 4 -->
	<examSet>
		<question>Make something up!?</question>
		<options>A) Different kinds of data structures are suited to different kinds of applications, and some are highly specialized to specific tasks. For example, B-trees are particularly well-suited for implementation of databases, while compiler implementations usually use hash tables to look up identifiers.

B) The Java collections framework (JCF) is a set of classes and interfaces that implement commonly reusable collection data structures. JCF is a part of SDK. Main interfaces JCF provides are: list, stack, queue, set, map.

C) Different kinds of data structures are suited to different kinds of applications, and some are highly specialized to specific tasks. For example, B-trees are particularly well-suited for implementation of databases, while compiler implementations usually use hash tables to look up identifiers.

D) The Java collections framework (JCF) is a set of classes and interfaces that implement commonly reusable collection data structures. JCF is a part of SDK. Main interfaces JCF provides are: list, stack, queue, set, map.
		</options>
		<answer>all options incorrect :/</answer>
	</examSet>


	<!-- <examSet> <profession></profession> <question></question> <answer> 
		</answer> </examSet> -->

</quiz>